carbikegamer.com 2019-05-22

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy of CarBikeGamer.com web site.

**

CarBikeGamer.com is firmly committed to the privacy of our users' personal information. Our staff, contractors and others who help us operate our web sites follow this policy on privacy and fair information practices for online activities of CarBikeGamer.com. We outline here the information-collection procedure and usage practices for our website, [www.CarBikeGamer.com](http://www.carbikegamer.com/). By using this website, you agree to accept this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policy may change over time as discussed below.

 **Your Information**

We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our web page. The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our web page.

 **Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

 **Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique 'cookie' on your browser.

 **Links**

CarBikeGamer.com also links to a wide variety of other web sites. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

 **Questions or Suggestions**

If you have any questions concerning the privacy policies of CarBikeGamer.com, please visit our Contact page.
